culvers.com 2019-05-07

# Privacy and Terms | Culver's

## Privacy

Culver Franchising System, LLC respects your privacy. We have provided this Privacy Policy to inform you of what information we collect and how we may use it.

We encourage parents to monitor their children’s online activities. Please instruct your children never to give out their names, addresses, phone numbers or e-mail addresses to anyone on the web without your permission. This Site complies with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), which governs information collected from children under 13. For more information about COPPA or children’s privacy, please visit [this site](https://www.consumer.ftc.gov/articles/0031-protecting-your-childs-privacy-online).

### The Information We Collect

As used in this Privacy Policy, "Personal Information" means any information that is linked to your identity such as your name, address, phone number (including mobile), birth day/month, demographic and geographic information, transaction information (including payment card and billing information), and/or email address. The site and/or mobile applications you entered as well as our third-party service providers may collect some or all of these types of Personal Information provided by you or on your behalf.

In order to register for MyCulver’s we require you to disclose your name, email address and zip code. Birth day/month and phone number are optional information you may disclose during MyCulver’s registration. In order to place a mobile order we require you to disclose your name, phone number, email address and payment information. Culver Franchising System, LLC will not collect any Personal Information from your visits to our Website or Mobile Application unless you provide your Personal Information to us voluntarily, and we will not require you to provide more information than is necessary to participate in our programs or services.

When you provide us with Personal Information, you are authorizing us to use that information in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy, which includes your right to limit our use of your Personal Information as described in this Policy. The Site you entered may also collect Personal Information from you about a third party (e.g., the Site might allow you to sign up family members for birthday offers, in which case we will need that person’s name and birth day/month). Please note that we use such information only for the specified purpose (e.g., for the birthday offer) and we will not leverage the third party information in any other way unless the third party contacts us or provides permission to do so.

We do not collect any personal information from kids visiting this Site, and a child’s participation in any of our online activities does not require that the child volunteer any personal information.

 Culvers.com does collect anonymous demographic and interest information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences and interests, in an effort to create a better visitor experience. You can turn off Google Analytics’ tracking at any time by using the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-ons [currently available](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

 Certain non-personal information may also be collected including products and locations you like, and product order history. Certain non-personal information is also recorded by the standard operation of Culver’s internet servers. This information is also used to provide an enhanced online experience for the visitor. Information tracked includes the type of operating system in use (e.g., Macintosh, Windows) and the type of browser being used by the visitor (e.g., Firefox, Internet Explorer, Google Chrome, Safari). In addition, we may use the following technology:

### Cookies

We do use limited “cookie” technology. Cookies are used to store bits of information on your computer to remember pages you have visited in the past. Culver Franchising System LLC and its third-party web applications do not use cookies to collect or store personally identifiable information. Third-party applications we use on our Site may attach cookies that fall outside Culver's privacy policy, such as the sharing platform AddThis. AddThis allows visitors to quickly and easily share our content on social networking services. The service collects certain anonymous information and may use it during visits to this website in order to provide visitors advertisements about goods and services. AddThis typically uses a cookie or a third-party web beacon to collect information. Visitors may [opt out](https://datacloudoptout.oracle.com/#optout) of data collection from AddThis at any time.

We also use Google Analytics which uses cookies to show how visitors have explored and engaged with our Site. This helps us improve our Website so visitors can find what they're looking for more quickly and easily. Visitors may [opt out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) of Google Analytics whenever they choose.

### Mobile Application

In addition to the above, when using the Culver’s Mobile Application, we may collect information including the type of mobile device and operating system being used. If location services are activated, the App will access the real-time geo-location of your device to find the nearest location or other search functionality. There may also be instances in which the device camera is activated upon approval for promotional purposes and game participation.

### Log Files

We may use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the Site, track user’s movement for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

### Links

This Website may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our Site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Website.

### The Way We Use Personal Information

When you supply Personal Information via our Site or mobile application, we will consolidate such Personal Information and use it for the purpose for which it was collected (e.g., to place mobile order or register for MyCulver’s) in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you opt in to receive our emails, we will also use it to contact you regarding Culver’s products or promotions as well as other products and services, which may be requested by or otherwise of interest to you. At any time, however, you may opt out of such future contact by unsubscribing from our database by following the unsubscribe instructions included in each promotional email.

### Third Parties

Our online services may offer links to websites that are not run by us but by third parties. If you visit one of these linked websites, you should read the website’s privacy policy, terms and conditions, and their other policies. We are not responsible for the policies and practices of third parties. Any information you give to those organizations is dealt with under their privacy policy, terms and conditions, and other policies.

We may also have providers of other apps, tools, widgets and plug-ins on our online services, such as Facebook “Like” buttons, which may also use automated methods to collect information about how you use these features. These organizations may use your information in line with their own policies. 

### Modifications

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy from time to time. We recommend that you visit our Website periodically to review any changes.

### Contact Information

We’d like to hear your questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy. Please reach out to our main office by submitting your comments here, calling 608-643-7980 Monday-Friday, 8 am to 5 pm CT or in writing by sending a letter or postcard to:

 Culver Franchising System, LLC (CFS)  
Attn: Marketing Dept.  
1240 Water Street  
Prairie du Sac, WI 53578

  Privacy Policy last updated: March 12, 2019

Copyright © 2019 Culver Franchising System, LLC. All Rights Reserved.

## Sweepstakes and Contests Privacy Policy

### The Information We Collect

As used in this Privacy Policy, "Personal Information" means any information that is linked to your identity such as your name, street address, telephone number, mobile number, screen name, age and/or email address. The Site you entered may collect some or all of these types of Personal Information through a sweepstakes, contest, game or promotion, or a registration form. Our website promotion may require registration and disclosure of particular information such as an email address in order for you to participate in sweepstakes, games or other activities. In order to register for our promotions, we require you to disclose your name, zip code, email address, birthdate and in some cases your mobile number. Culver Franchising System, LLC will not collect any Personal Information from your visits to our Website unless you provide your Personal Information to us voluntarily, and we will not require you to provide more information than is necessary to participate in our promotions. We also do not collect financial or other sensitive data information about our users.

When you provide us with Personal Information, you are authorizing us to use that information in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy, which includes your right to limit our use of your Personal Information as described in this Policy.

The Site you entered may also collect Personal Information from you about a third party (e.g., the Site might allow you to send an email or message to a friend, in which case we will need that person's name and email address). Please note that we use such information only for the specified purpose (e.g., to deliver the email message) and we will not contact the third party again by email unless and until the third party contacts us or provides permission to do so.

### The Way We Use Personal Information

When you supply Personal Information at Culver’s Website, we will consolidate such Personal Information and use it for the purpose for which it was collected (e.g., to enter you in a sweepstakes or to fulfill the delivery of a sweepstakes prize) in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you opt in to receive our eClub, we will also use it to contact you regarding Culver’s products or promotions as well as other products and services, which may be requested by or otherwise of interest to you. At any time, however, you may opt out of such future contact by unsubscribing from our database by following the unsubscribe instructions included in each promotional email.

### With Whom We May Share Information

In the course of doing business, we employ other companies to perform a variety of functions on our behalf. For example, we may share Personal Information including email address or mailing address with fulfillment houses and other service providers to allow delivery of prizes. These third parties may have access to your Personal Information if it is needed to perform their functions for Culver Franchising System, LLC but they are not authorized by us to use your Personal Information in any way other than the intended use within the promotion. We do not share your Personal Information including email address with any third parties who are not service providers.

We also may share aggregate, non-personally identifiable information about our users with third parties. For example, we may tell a business partner the number of people that entered a contest, but we do not disclose Personal Information about such contestants in violation of this Privacy Policy.

### Important Note about Children's Information

Please note that we do not collect any Personal Information from any person under the age of thirteen (13) years of age. In addition, we reserve the right to limit participation in particular programs or promotions to visitors eighteen (18) years of age, twenty one (21) years of age, or older.

© 2019 Culver Franchising System, LLC

## Terms of Use

Your access to and use of this site is subject to this Visitor Agreement and all applicable laws. By accessing and browsing this Site, you accept, without limitation or qualification, this Visitor Agreement. We may at any time revise this Visitor Agreement and you are bound by any such revisions. We suggest that you periodically visit this page to review the Visitor Agreement.

This Site contains many of the valuable trademarks owned and used by Culver Franchising System, LLC to distinguish its quality products and services. These trademarks and related propriety property are protected from copying and simulation under national and international laws and are not to be reproduced or copied without our prior written permission. The Site many also contain references to other company, brand and product names. These company, brand and product names are used for identification purposes only and may be the trademarks of their respective owners.

The graphic images, buttons and text contained in this Website are the exclusive property of Culver's and, except for personal use, may not be copied, distributed or transmitted in any form or by any mean, electronic, mechanical, photocopying, recording or otherwise, without prior permission. The content, arrangement and layout of the Site, including but not limited to, the trademarks, service marks, package designs, text, and content, are proprietary and are protected from copying, imitation, communication or simulation under domestic and international laws and are not to be reproduced, communicated, displayed, distributed, or transmitted without our prior written permission.

To place a mobile order you must provide valid payment card and billing information. Such information will be collected by Culver’s and/or a third party. Your information will be collected and used in accordance with Culver’s Privacy Policy. We use third party providers and may accept various third party services to process payments. When you purchase products through mobile ordering, prices will be made clear during the order process. You agree to pay the price that is stated at the time of your order, as well as any applicable taxes. You also agree to have your payment card billed for the total amount displayed at check out when you click ‘Check In’ during your mobile order. Payment cards will not be billed unless you click ‘Check In’ to process your mobile order. Mobile ordering is available at participating restaurant locations.

We strive to ensure that the information contained in this Site is accurate and reliable. However, errors may sometimes occur. Therefore, to the fullest extent permissible pursuant to applicable law, we disclaim any warranty, express or implied, as to matter whatsoever relating to this Site. We are not responsible for any damages or injuries caused by use of this Site, including without limitation, viruses, omissions or misstatements. We shall not be liable for any direct or indirect, special, consequential or incidental damages that result from your use or inability to use this Site.

The Visitor Agreement shall be governed by the laws of the State of Wisconsin, without giving effect to any principles of conflicts of law. You agree that any action at law or equity arising out of or related to your use of this Site must be filed only in the state and federal courts located in the state of Wisconsin, and you submit to personal jurisdiction of such courts.
